[
  {
    "question": "Collections Framework is present in __________ package.",
    "answer": "java.util"
  },
  {
    "question": "__________ Collection allows duplicate elements.",
    "answer": "List"
  },
  {
    "question": "__________ Collection does NOT allow duplicate elements.",
    "answer": "Set"
  },
  {
    "question": "__________ interface stores data in key-value pairs.",
    "answer": "Map"
  },
  {
    "question": "____________ is the parent interface of Collection.",
    "answer": "Iterable"
  },
  {
    "question": "___________ List implementation is best for frequent insertions and deletions?",
    "answer": "LinkedList"
  },
  {
    "question": "___________ List implementation is best for frequent reading and searching?",
    "answer": "ArrayList"
  },
  {
    "question": "___________ List implementation is best for thread-safe operation?",
    "answer": "Vector"
  },
  {
    "question": "__________ is a bidirectional cursor that can traverse a List in both forward and backward directions.",
    "answer": "ListIterator"
  },
  {
    "question": "One _________ interface in particular is not considered to be a true Collection.",
    "answer": "Map"
  },
  {
    "question": "__________ cursor is applicable to all Collection classes in Java.",
    "answer": "Iterator"
  },
  {
    "question": "__________ does NOT allow null elements.",
    "answer": "TreeSet"
  },
  {
    "question": "Natural sorting is achieved using __________ interface.",
    "answer": "Comparable"
  },
  {
    "question": "Customized sorting is achieved using __________ interface.",
    "answer": "Comparator"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the Ordered Collection ___________",
    "answer": "List"
  },
  {
    "question": "The map key value pair also knows as _______",
    "answer": "Entry"
  },
  {
    "question": "When we insert the duplicate data in Set it throws an error ______(true/false)",
    "answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "question": "In TreeMap by default the data sorted based on values ________(true/false)",
    "answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is it List allows multiple null data insertion ________(yes/no)",
    "answer": "yes"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is it Set allows multiple null data insertion ________(yes/no)",
    "answer": "no"
  }
]
